posturown.com 2014-04-02

# Privacy Policy

If you leave a comment, the information you provide for your name, email address and website URL will be stored in a database on a hosted server. Please refer to my [comments policy](http://www.posturown.com/comments-policy/ "Comments Policy") concerning my right to contact you.

I use various forms of tracking services. Some of the services may reveal personal data to some extent. I will have access to general details, in addition to the above, such as the IP address you are connected with, your browser, your screen resolution, the last website you were viewing and the pages you read on my blog.

Subscriptions to RSS feeds are anonymous. For email subscriptions, the service is provided by FeedBurner (a part of Google), and the information is not anonymous.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this website, if we serve ads at all. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/ "Network Advertising Initiative").

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site for the Google AdSense program (when ads are displayed). Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/ "Privacy Center") page.

Your personal data will be kept as secure as possible. It will not be shared or sold to other parties. I will delete any personal information which you identify upon your request via the contact page.
